(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 1,
"subtitles": 2
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
重大告知
Major Announcement
Monster
12時を少し過ぎる頃
About the time it's just past 12 o'clock
Ah ha, 酷なモンスター
Ah ha, a cruel monster
月明かり 草木眠る頃
When the moonlight shines and the flora sleeps
Ah ha, 蘇る
Ah ha, it revives
君の叫びで
With your scream
僕は目覚める
I awaken
今宵の闇へ
Into the darkness of tonight
君を誘うモンスター
The monster that invites you
凍りつく夜が作り出す
Created by the freezing night
We are 君の後ろ
We are right behind you
気付いた時はもう閉じ込める
By the time you notice, you're already trapped
Monster 逃げ場はない
Monster, there's no escape
Just watch 君の手を
Just watch, your hand...
愛の手を抱いて眠りたい
I want to sleep holding your hand of love
あなたがいたから生まれた
I was born because you were there
君が好きなんだ
I love you.
夜が明けるまで近くにいよう
Let's stay close until the dawn breaks.
僕の記憶が全て消えても
Even if all my memories were to fade away,
生まれ変わったらまた君を探す
If I'm reborn, I'll look for you again.
見かけじゃなくて心を抱いて
Embracing your heart, not just your appearance,
満月の夜君を見つけたモンスター
On a full moon night, the monster found you.
止まらない部屋に這い込む
Slithering into a room that never stops,
足音が徐々に近くなる今動けない
Footsteps are gradually getting closer, now I can't move.
このスリル止められない怖がらせたい
I can't stop this thrill, I want to scare you.
だけど本当は君が好きなんだ
But the truth is, I love you.
朝が見えるまで隣にいよう
Let's stay together until morning comes.
一万年の愛を叫ぼう
Let's shout out a love that lasts ten thousand years.
生まれ変わってもまた君を探すモンスター
Even if I'm reborn, the monster will look for you again.
12時を少し過ぎる頃月明かり草木眠る頃
Just a little after midnight, when the moonlight rests upon the sleeping plants,
君の涙で僕は目覚める
I wake up at the sound of your tears.
今宵の闇へ君を連れ出す
I'll take you away into tonight's darkness.
僕の記憶が全て消えても
Even if all my memories were to fade away,
生まれ変わったらまた君を探す
If I'm reborn, I'll look for you again.
見かけじゃなくて心を抱いて
Embracing your heart, not just your appearance,
満月の夜君を見つけたモンスター
On a full moon night, the monster found you.
モンスター
Monster
愛、参り、ディスコミュ まるで狂気の花
Love, coming, discommu, like a flower of madness
泣きそうに、悲しそうに あなたに伝えたい
Feeling like crying, feeling so sad, I want to tell you
I only love you それは魔法の言葉
I only love you, those are the magic words
消えそうに、優しそうに あなたに伝えたい
Faintly, and so tenderly, I want to tell you
幸せな蝶になったって 瞬きで宙に飛んじゃって
Even if I become a happy butterfly, I'll fly into the sky in a blink,
並ばぬ願い託して 受けて止めて認めて
Entrusting my unparalleled wishes, accept them, catch them, and recognize them.
揺れるファイヤー叫ぶファイハイ 私染まれば
Swaying fire, shouting 'fire high', if I am dyed,
隣の幸せとか積もる情熱をあげる
I'll give you the happiness beside me and the passion that builds up.
揺れるファイヤー叫ぶファイハイ 闇を照らすのだ
Swaying fire, shouting 'fire high', I will light up the darkness
イカれた憎しみさえ届く衝撃をくれるか
Will you give me a shock that reaches even my crazy hatred?
独りは耐えうるものね 痛みは愛することね
Being alone is something that can be endured, and pain is a way of loving,
二人は今を生きる どこまで
The two of us live in the present, no matter how far.
ファイヤー揺れるファイヤー 二人染まれば
Fire, swaying fire, if we are both dyed,
あなたに
To you
その瞳 幸あれ
May your eyes be blessed
揺れるファイヤー 燃えるファイヤーウェイ
Swaying fire, burning fire way
駆けて行きましょう
Let's run forth
あてどないままに
Aimlessly
その命 差し出せ
Offer up that life
まさに
Truly
受け止めて
Accept it
認めて
Acknowledge it
揺れるファイヤー 叫ぶファイヤーハイ
Swaying fire, shouting fire high
私 誘えば
If I invite you
二人の幸せとか深く情熱が宿る
Deep passion dwells in the happiness of two
揺れるファイヤー 燃えるファイヤーウェイ
Swaying fire, burning fire way
駆けて行きましょう
Let's run forth
怒りと憎しみさえ届く 衝撃をくれる
Even anger and hatred reach, giving a shock
カモン
Come on
人は耐えうるものね
Humans can endure, can't they?
痛みは愛することで
Pain is by loving
二人は今を生きる
Two people live for the now
どこまで
No matter how far
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you very much!
はぁー。まずは2曲お届けしました。
Whew. First, I've delivered two songs.
えー、姫たちもありがとうございます。
Um, thank you to the princesses as well.
ということで、6周年ライブへようこそ！
And so, welcome to the 6th anniversary live!
わーい！
Yay!
はぁー。ついに6周年になりました。
Whew. It's finally been 6 years.
えーと、皆さんのコメントを読みたいと思います。
Um, I'd like to read everyone's comments.
パチパチ、すいちゃん、えー、かっこいい、ありがとう。
Clap clap, Sui-chan, um, "cool", thank you.
かっこよかった、ありがとう。
You were cool, thank you.
あー、そうかっこよさ全開でね、一番最初は王子様をやらせていただきました。
Ah, yes, with full-on coolness, I played the prince at the very beginning.
姫たちよ。
My princesses.
はい。そして今日は、えー、6周年でもあるんですけれども、
Yes. And today is the 6th anniversary,
と同時に、誕生日でもあるんです！わーい！
But at the same time, it's also my birthday! Yay!
だ。18歳になりました。
Tada. I've turned 18.
ついに18歳になりましたよ、皆さん。わー。
I've finally turned 18, everyone. Wow.
えー、18.6歳か。
Um, 18.6 years old, huh.
いや、時の流れは本当に早いですね。
Boy, time really flies.
えー、今日までね、活動を続けられてるのも皆さんのおかげです。本当にありがとうございます。
Um, it's thanks to all of you that I've been able to continue my activities until today. Thank you so very much.
えー、最初のね、2曲は舞踏会をイメージして、えー、やってみました。
Um, for the first two songs, I tried doing them with a ballroom image.
7年目...
7th year...
7年目の最初を飾る、素敵なライブにしようと思ってますので、今日は楽しんでいってください！
I'm planning to make this a wonderful live performance to kick off the 7th year, so please enjoy yourself today!
えー、そして皆さん、えー、重大告知その1としてですね、匂わせツイートをしたと思うんですけど、
Um, and everyone, as major announcement number one, I think I made a suggestive tweet,
わかるかな？ね？わかるよね、何が変わったのか。
I wonder if you can tell? Right? You can tell, right? What's changed.
ちょっと...どう？
Wait... How is it?
わかる？
Can you tell?
あれ？あんまわか...あれ？あんまわかってない、もしkして。
Wait? You don't really... Huh? Maybe you haven't really noticed.
わかんないなー。「髪切った？」えー、いやいやいや。
You don't know? "Did you cut your hair?" Um, no, no, no.
あのー、ちょっとメイクをちょっと変えてみたんだけど。新しい化粧品にしてみたんだけど。
Um, I tried changing my makeup a bit. I tried using some new cosmetics.
ねえ。あのまつ毛とかね、新しいマスカラにしてみたんだけどね。はい、ウインク。
Right. My eyelashes and stuff, I tried a new mascara. Okay, wink.
どう？
How is it?
えー？「シャンプー変えた？」いや、シャンプーは一緒。
Eh? "Did you change your shampoo?" No, the shampoo is the same.
シャンプーは一緒なの。
The shampoo is the same.
わかんねえなあ。えー？
You don't know, huh. Eh?
そんな...ま、ということで
Well... Anyway,
えー、メイクがちょっとだけ新しくなりました。
Um, my makeup has become just a little bit newer.
えー、この新しいメイクで撮影会をですね、このライブが終わった後、メン限でやりますので、皆さんぜひ見に来てくださいね。
Um, after this live performance, I'll be doing a photo session with this new makeup in a members-only stream, so please come and watch it.
えー、あと、なんか台本が更新されたぞ。
Um, also, looks like the script has been updated.
トレンド1位なんですか？
I'm #1 on trending?
トレンド1位になったの？
Did it reach #1 on trending?
おおー！ありがとうございます。
Ohhh! Thank you so much.
やったー！ありがとうみんな。
Yay! Thank you everyone.
いや、まだまだ、呟いてください。
No, keep on tweeting.
もうトレンド1位より上を目指しましょう。
Let's aim for even higher than #1 on trending.
はい。えー、そして、えー、重大告知1つ目はこのメイクがちょっと変わったよだったんですけど、
Yes. Um, and, major announcement number one was that this makeup changed a bit,
まだ、まだ重大告知ありますのでね、ぜひ最後まで見てください。
But there are still more major announcements to come, so please watch until the end.
ではそろそろ、えー、次の曲行っちゃってもいいかなー？
Well, is it okay if I move on to the next song soon?
いいかなー！？
Is it okay!?
いいよ。ありがとうございます。
It's okay. Thank you very much.
それでは参りたいと思います。
Well then, I'd like to get started.
次の曲は「午夜の待ち合わせ」で行きましょう！
Let's go with the next song, "Midnight Meeting"!
午夜の待ち合わせ 照準を 僕は片手に持っている
A midnight meeting, I hold the aim in one hand
午夜の待ち合わせ 作詞・作曲：シュンタロウ
Midnight Meeting / Lyrics & Composition: Shuntaro
午後の待ち合わせ
作詞・作曲 カワイヒデヒロ
Afternoon Rendezvous
Lyrics & Composition: Hidehiro Kawai
歌う君の場所へ足を早め向かっている
I'm heading towards where you're singing, quickening my pace
チクタクチクタクと...
Tick-tock, tick-tock...
焦る鼓動を急かしてだけ
Just rushing my racing heart
チクタクチクタクと...
Tick-tock, tick-tock...
留まる気配もなく進んでいく
Moving forward without a sign of stopping
誰のものでもない部屋で
In a room that belongs to no one
響かせた手を伸ばしてる
Stretching out my hands that I made resonate
サイダー僕の居場所は
Cider, the place where I belong...
誰にも分からず
...is known to no one
チクタクチクタクと
Tick-tock, tick-tock
終わりと始まりの境目
The boundary between the end and the beginning
チクタクチクタクと
Tick-tock, tick-tock
すべてが重なった
Everything overlapped
Hey, Go Step! 待っていた
Hey, Go Step! I was waiting...
眩暈るほどの悲しみを
...for a sadness that makes my head spin
Hey, Go Step! 待っていた
Hey, Go Step! I was waiting...
涙するほどの幸福も
...even for a happiness that brings tears
誰のものでもない部屋で
In a room that belongs to no one
響かせた手を伸ばしてる
Stretching out my hands that I made resonate
サイダー僕の居場所は
Cider, the place where I belong...
誰にも分からず
...is known to no one
チクタクチクタクと
Tick-tock, tick-tock
騙し騙しの日々を
Spending the days getting by somehow
チクタクチクタクと
Tick-tock, tick-tock
進まない僕を
Me, who isn't moving forward...
チクタクチクタクと
Tick-tock, tick-tock
責め立てるように
...as if to reproach me
チクタクチクタクと
Tick-tock, tick-tock
すべてが重なった
Everything overlapped
Hey, Go Step! 待っていた
Hey, Go Step! I was waiting...
薄暗い部屋 一人きり
...all alone in a dim room
Hey, Go Step! 待っていた
Hey, Go Step! I was waiting...
ドアを蹴破る その時を
...for that moment to kick down the door
Hey, Go Step! 待っていた
Hey, Go Step! I was waiting...
薄暗い部屋 一人きり
...all alone in a dim room
Hey, Go Step! 待っていた
Hey, Go Step! I was waiting...
もう恐れることないよ
There's nothing to fear anymore
弾丸込めた照準を
Standing with aim loaded with bullets
持って立って 閉ざされたドアを蹴破った
I kicked down the closed door
突きつけた銃口が
The muzzle I pointed at me
跳ねて昨日の僕を貫いた
Rebounded and pierced through the yesterday's me
おやすみ その絶望を受け取って
Good night, take that despair
明日への僕は歩き出した
And I've started walking towards tomorrow
また今夜 待ち合わせを
Let's meet again tonight
アウトサイダー
作詞・作曲 Eve
Outsider
Lyrics & Composition: Eve
ねえねえこの世界を どっかひっくり返したくて
Hey, hey, I want to turn this world upside down somehow
せいぜい時間なんて ありゃしやしないが
At most, I don't really have any time
まあまあそんなんで 少年少女揃いまして
Well, well, with that, boys and girls have gathered
唸り始めた快進撃さ
And the charge has begun with a roar
天才で人外で 凡庸な
A genius, inhuman, and mundane
最低で最高な 相棒さ
The worst and best partner
単純で明快な 考えが
Simple and clear thoughts
僕をここで 覚ましていってくれないか
Won't you wake me up right here?
今この身をもって 重石をとって
Now, taking this body and removing the weight
君にだけにしか できないことあんだ
There's something only you can do
ここにいなくて 慰めなんていらないや
You're not here, and I don't need any comfort
派手なチリになって しまわぬように
So that you don't become just flashy dust
その名を隠して ここに現れたのさ
You appeared here, hiding that name
むさぼってる奴らを
Probing those who are devouring
さぐってずっと 笑って笑って
Always laughing, laughing
ああ 消耗ないな
Ah, it's so exhausting
勝手にやってる文句ばっか 否定したって泣いたって
Complaining as they please, even if you deny it or cry
誰かのせいしたって
Even if you blame someone else
ああ フラッシュバックして
Ah, flashing back
初心者の振舞いが 感情も根性も
A beginner's behavior, both emotion and spirit
散ってしまいました
Have scattered away
思い出したくない一日は
The days I don't want to remember
ここに吐き出してしまえよ
Just spit them out here
いらんもんを全部捨て去って
Throw away all the things you don't need
僕をここで 壊してくれないか
Won't you break me right here?
今は鐘を持って 口を結んで
Now holding the bell, lips sealed
染み付いた夜の 傷が癒えないのなら
If the wounds from the ingrained night won't heal
無理に見せないで こんなはずなんていらないや
Don't force yourself to show them, I don't need things like this
全て失って しまわぬように
So that you don't lose everything
変わらぬものが ここにあるとするならば
If there is something unchanging here
夜が明ける前に 存在を言ってしまおうよ
Let's declare our existence before the night breaks
白と黒の色もない 世界に溢れた
Overflowing into a world with no white or black
愛も全部ないよ その世界に涙した
There's no love at all, I cried in that world
心の庭 決して許してはくれないから
Because the garden of the heart will never forgive
感極まり切って 火を放ち切って
Overwhelmed with emotion, setting it all on fire
明日を迎えることが
Greeting tomorrow...
されたのは
...was done.
救われてたかな それでも僕は
I wonder if I was saved? Even so, I...
今この身を以って
Taking this body now,
面白を採って
taking what's interesting,
君にでしかできない理なら
if it's a truth only you can achieve,
ここに鳴いていて
then cry out here.
慰めなんていらないや
I don't need any comfort.
果てになってしまうの様に
As if coming to an end,
その名を隠してここに現れたのさ
I appeared here, hiding that name.
貪ってる奴らを
Those who are devouring,
探って穿って 曝け出して
probe them, dig deep, and expose them.
その小さな勇気が 僕の胸を焦がすから
Because that small bit of courage scorches my chest.
こいかぜ (Short Ver.)
Koikaze (Short Ver.)
渇いた風が 心 通り抜ける
A dry wind passes through my heart,
溢れる思い 連れ去ってほしい
I want it to take away these overflowing feelings.
二人の影 何気ない会話も
Even our shadows and casual conversation,
嫉妬してる 切なくなる
I'm jealous, it hurts...
これが恋なの？
Is this love?
あなたしか見えなくなって
I can only see you,
想い育ててゆくばかり
and my feelings just keep growing.
苦しくて
It's so painful,
見せかけの笑顔も もう作れないなんて
that I can't even make a fake smile anymore.
満ちては欠ける想いが今 愛しくて溢れ出すの
Feelings that wax and wane are now so dear they're overflowing.
舞い戻る風の踊る中で
In the dancing wind that swirls back,
めぐり逢えたこの奇跡が
this miracle of our meeting,
遥かな大地を越えて
crosses the distant earth.
あなたと未来へ 歩きたいの
I want to walk towards the future with you.
君だけを想う気持ち
How I feel only about you,
伝えられる勇気が 私にあれば
if I only had the courage to tell you...
切ない夜に さよならできる
I could say goodbye to these painful nights.
願いをこめて Wish my love
With a prayer, Wish my love,
踏み出す力ください
please give me the strength to take a step forward.
楓さん、今日は来てくれてありがとうございます！
Kaede-san, thank you so much for coming today!
お招きいただきありがとうございます。
Thank you for having me.
シンデレラガールズの高垣楓です。
I'm Kaede Takagaki from Cinderella Girls.
すいせいさん、
Suisei-san,
デビュー6周年、そしてお誕生日おめでとうございます。
congratulations on your 6th anniversary and birthday.
楓さんと「こいかぜ」一緒に歌えて本当に嬉しいです！
I'm so happy to be able to sing 'Koikaze' with you, Kaede-san!
私もすいせいさんとご一緒できてすごく嬉しかったです。
I was also very happy to be with you, Suisei-san.
とっても素敵な歌声で。
You have such a wonderful singing voice.
え～、ありがとうございます！
Aww, thank you so much!
楓さんのことずっと応援していて大好きだったので、
I've been a fan and have loved Kaede-san for a long time,
今回のコラボができたことが夢みたいです。
so being able to do this collaboration feels like a dream.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you.
こんなお祝いの場に呼んでいただけて、こちらこそ光栄ですよ。
It's my honor to be invited to such a celebratory occasion.
今回このコラボが実現したのは、私たちのコラボ曲もあるからなんですよね。
The reason this collaboration happened is that we also have a collab song together, right?
ええ。
Yes.
お互いの良さが現れた、とっても素敵な楽曲になりましたね。
It turned out to be a wonderful song that brings out the best in both of us.
皆さんもぜひ楽しんでください。
Everyone, please look forward to it and enjoy.
それでは聴いてください。せーの…
Then, please listen. Ready...
ジュビリー！
Jubilee!
始まるよ ジュビリー
It's beginning, Jubilee.
超新星と行進しよう
Let's march with the supernova
合図待っているフレーズを確かめて
Confirm the phrases waiting for the signal
目を合わせた
Our eyes met
きっと太陽は今ごろ夢の中
The sun must be in a dream by now
ようこそパレードへ
Welcome to the parade
チケットはいらない
No ticket required
君がそこにいる
You are there
音楽が始まる
The music begins
高らかにホーンズアップ
Raise your horns high
めくるめくようなフレーズは一夜のトロイメライ
The dizzying phrases are a one-night Träumerei
あでやかなトランペット 夜空を渡って
A glamorous trumpet crosses the night sky
照れ屋の月さえ顔を出すんだ
Even the shy moon shows its face
さながら僕らは天の川
We are just like the Milky Way
宇宙まで響くドラムメジャー
Drum major echoing to the universe
星の街
Stellar City (Hoshi no Machi)
恋の風
Wind of Love (Koi no Kaze)
出会いは音楽になってまた咲く
Our encounter becomes music and blooms again
銀河系の隅っこで
At the corner of the galaxy
同じ呼吸と同じハーモニー
Same breath and same harmony
ほら ほら 奇跡はここにある
Look, look, the miracle is here
始まるよジュビリー
It's starting, Jubilee
幸杯よりも先に Let the music swing and sing
Before the toast, let the music swing and sing
星屑のチューニング秘めて点呼最高潮
Hiding stardust tuning, the roll call is at its peak
ラインもっと遠く 遠く
Line even further, further
終わらないジュビリー
Unending Jubilee
一色十色デシベルアッペル Let the music swing and sing
Ten colors, decibel appeal, let the music swing and sing
探してよ Who is me?
Search for me, who is me?
超新星と行進しよう ずっと遠く 遠く
Let's march with the supernova, far, far away
今夜君の涙と 僕の弱さが出会って
Tonight your tears and my weakness meet
歌になればいいなって笑う
I smile, hoping it becomes a song
待ちきれないセッションはゴーオン
The session we can't wait for goes on
未完成な夜を救いたいから
Because I want to save the unfinished night
ほら まだ 奇跡を 僕らの奇跡を祈って歌うよ
Look, still, praying for the miracle, our miracle, I'll sing
続けようジュビリー 幸杯よりも先に Let the music swing and sing
Let's continue Jubilee, before the toast, let the music swing
ありえない瞬間速度 革命前夜マーク
Impossible speed, marking the eve of the revolution
もっと遠く 遠く
Even further, further
終わらないジュビリー 最高潮かなで Let the music swing and sing
Unending Jubilee, let the music swing and sing
探してよ Who is me? 超新星と行進しよう
Search for me, who is me? Let's march with the supernova
ずっと遠く 遠く 君と遠くまで
Far, far away, far away with you
またデレステでお目に掛かりましょう
Let's meet again in Deresute
ありがとうございました
Thank you very much!
バイバーイ
Bye-bye!
はい！
Yes!
ということで、えー、高垣楓さんと新曲『ジュビリー』
So, with Takagaki Kaede-san, the new song 'Jubilee'...
そして高垣楓さんの、えー、ソロ曲『恋の風』をお届けさせていただきました
...and Takagaki Kaede-san's solo song 'Koi no Kaze' were delivered.
本当に本当に夢のような時間で、本当に楓さんありがとうございました
It was truly a dream-like time. Thank you so much, Kaede-san.
楓さん！ありがとうございました！
Kaede-san! Thank you very much!
本当に指の先まで、すごいパフォーマンスがお綺麗で
Her performance was so beautiful, down to her fingertips.
それに並び立てるようにと、頑張って躍らせていただきました
I did my best to dance so I could stand alongside her.
ぜひとも、ぜひともね、この後の重大告知も皆さん心して、心してくださいね！
Stay tuned for the major announcement coming up next!
それでは！
And now!
えー、では、重大告知、2つ目！
And now, for the second major announcement!
告知しちゃいたいと思います。こちら！
I'd like to announce it. Here it is!
今回、初披露させていただいた、星街すいせい・高垣楓によるコラボ楽曲、『ジュビリー』が、
The collaboration song "Jubilee" by Suisei Hoshimachi and Kaede Takagaki, which was performed for the first time today,
3月23日15時よりデレステのゲーム内イベントにて登場します！
...will appear in the DereSte in-game event from March 23rd at 3:00 PM!
イベントのコミュや報酬Sレアカードに、私、星街すいせいが登場します！
I, Suisei Hoshimachi, will appear in the event stories and as an S-Rare reward card!
なんて可愛いの、私も楓さんも。ありがとう。
How cute we both are, Kaede-san and I. Thank you.
そして、同じく明日、3月23日15時より、
And also tomorrow, March 23rd at 3:00 PM,
星街すいせいと高垣楓がSSレアアイドルとして登場するコラボガシャが登場です！
...a collaboration gacha featuring Suisei Hoshimachi and Kaede Takagaki as SS Rare idols will be available!
衣装は、私達二人のためにデザインされた特別な衣装になっていますので、是非デレステでゲットしてみて下さい。
The outfits were specially designed for the two of us, so please try to get them in DereSte.
本当に色んな関係者の方々のお力添えのおかげで、このような夢のようなお衣装が叶っております。本当にありがとうございます。
Thanks to the support of many people involved, these dream-like outfits have become a reality. Thank you very much.
そして、えー、第2回デレステコラボ配信が決定しました！
And, we've decided to hold a second DereSte collaboration stream!
3月26日20時から私のチャンネルで行う予定ですので、是非見に来て下さい。
It's scheduled for March 26th at 8:00 PM on my channel, so please come and watch.
先程発表したコラボ楽曲『ジュビリー』のMVやコラボガシャで登場するSSレアなども紹介します。
I'll be introducing the MV for the collaboration song "Jubilee" and the SS Rare idols from the collaboration gacha.
その他、第1回配信で遊びきれなかったライブなども遊んでいくので、お楽しみに。
I'll also be playing songs that I couldn't get to in the first stream, so look forward to it.
そして、最後！
And finally!
コラボ楽曲『ジュビリー』が3月24日日曜日0時より、各音楽配信サービスでの配信が決定しました！
The collaboration song "Jubilee" will be available on various music streaming services starting Sunday, March 24th at midnight!
そう、作詞・作曲・編曲は我らがTaku Inoue、イノタクさんです。
That's right, the lyrics, composition, and arrangement are by our very own Taku Inoue, Inotaku-san.
是非配信でもたくさん聴いて下さい！
Please listen to it a lot on streaming services too!
はい、ありがとうございました。立て続けのデレステ情報でしたが、
All right, thank you very much. That was a lot of DereSte info all at once, but...
皆さん是非明日からイベント、そしてガシャが始まりますので、是非是非デレステで遊んでみて下さいね。
...the event and gacha start tomorrow, so please do play DereSte, everyone.
ということで、えー、次の曲に行きたいと思います。定位置、定位置ね。定位置に戻って...
And now, I'd like to move on to the next song. Back to my position, my position. Returning to my position...
それでは、後半戦も盛り上がっていきましょう！
Well then, let's keep the energy up for the second half!
遠ざかる夜の雑踏、まるでトイボックス、黙って待って...
The receding crowd of the night, like a toy box, wait in silence...
路地裏ネオンのマーケット。
A neon market in the back alley.
なれない文字と言語いなして、秘密裏にコードそっと交わして...
Handling unfamiliar letters and languages, quietly exchanging codes in secret...
この街が今日のターゲット。
This city is today's target.
視界を遮るスポット、控えなき個の人口プラットフォーム。
Spots that obstruct the view, an unreserved personal population platform.
見逃し込んだ矢印、あれなら二人で十分。
An arrow missed, that would be enough for two.
不自然な呼吸も下ろして、聞き飽きない澄ました顔で、
Let down your unnatural breathing, with a composed face you never tire of hearing,
シリンダー出したその手。
The hand that brought out the cylinder.
今宵、ありたけの衝動さらって...
Tonight, take all the impulses you can...
さあ始めようか。
Come on, let's get started.
全てからポーカー、終わりのない。
Poker from everything, with no end.
夜を明ける。
Bringing in the dawn.
合図して世界の秘密暴く、ちょっと響いてSOS。
Give the signal and uncover the world's secrets, echoing a little SOS.
退屈なスパイラル見透かして、アンロックで。
See through the boring spiral, and unlock it.
反撃だ控えの海潜って、パス接続で点と線。
It's a counterattack, dive into the sea of reserves, connecting dots and lines with a pass.
カオティックな音に乗せて。
Ride on the chaotic sound.
合図して世界の秘密暴く、今日もめぐろデフォルメ。
Give the signal and uncover the world's secrets, today again, a deformed rotation.
錆び付いて動かない鍵も、アンロックで。
Even keys that are rusted and won't move, unlock them.
迎撃だ控えの海を泳いで、僕のペースとフェイクの乱反射。
It's an interception, swim through the sea of reserves, my pace and the diffuse reflection of fakes.
カオティックな音で踊って、
Dance to the chaotic sound,
さあ陽が昇るまで。
Until the sun rises.
陽が昇るまで。
静寂の奔流に空気孕んで、この部屋の闇もそっと崩して... 右には罠、左側裏にサメ。
The air swells in the torrent of silence, quietly breaking the darkness of this room... Traps on the right, sharks behind the left.
キッチュな匂い一人きり、もっと練習しといて。
The kitschy smell, all alone, practice some more.
狂いに狂ってチューニング。
Crazy tuning, out of control.
情動の九分通り、答えはずっと192で。
Ninety percent of the emotion, the answer is always 192.
過剰なショーの空砲、ブーバーじゃないの。
The blank fire of an excessive show, it's not a Boober.
淀んだラスト15、思考を拒んだ心臓スナイパー。
The stagnant last 15, the heart sniper that refused to think.
脅したっていいさ。
It's okay to threaten.
ありたけの衝動さらって...
Take all the impulses you can...
さあどうしようか。
Now, what should we do?
負け筋のポーカー、染めてもまだ。
Poker on the losing track, even if dyed,
笑ったまま。
Still smiling.
合図して世界の秘密暴く、1.2.3.で...
Give the signal and uncover the world's secrets, on 1, 2, 3...
パパパパッパンクスのバイブスは
The pa-pa-pa-pa punks' vibes are
未だくすぶってるのさ
still smoldering.
流星を待って迎える衝動
Waiting for a meteor, welcoming the impulse,
逆転のラストパス
the final pass for a comeback.
カオティックな音に乗せて
Riding on the chaotic sound,
合図して世界を攫うよ
I'll signal and snatch the world away.
カーテンコールで錆び付いた脳内を
My brain, rusted at the curtain call,
アンロックして
will be unlocked.
バイバイバイ 聖の海を泳いで
Bye bye bye, swimming in the holy sea,
僕のフェーズは最高潮
my phase is at its peak.
ハイウェイで遊ぼうぜ 走って
Let's play on the highway, running,
カオティックな音で踊って
dancing to the chaotic sound,
HIGHになるまで
Until we're HIGH.
洒落た夜に 溢れたメロディー
Overflowing melody on a stylish night,
絡まってんのに 愛は解けてゆく
though it's entangled, love is unraveling.
いつだってそうに 心配したがってるのに
It's always like that, even though I want to worry,
fake face dance music 夜明けまで踊っている
fake face dance music, dancing until dawn.
fake face dance music
作詞・作曲：TAKU INOUE
Lyrics & Composition: TAKU INOUE
いつだって情緒不安定なことあることも言っちゃってんだ
I even say that I'm sometimes emotionally unstable,
行き場のないこの世界では 稀に見かける愛を信じ続けてる
in this world with nowhere to go, I keep believing in the rare love I find.
朝食かてらのばかばかしい
The ridiculous
ニュースで誰かが笑ってた
breakfast-time news had someone laughing.
その時からなのか
Maybe it was from then,
知ってる世界じゃなくなっていた
it was no longer the world I knew.
本当に可笑しな人生ね
It's a truly funny life, isn't it?
それでも拝した運命で
Even so, with the fate I bowed to,
あなたにこの心 拝借された
my heart was borrowed by you.
晴れたテンポに 跳ねたメロディ
A bouncing melody to a sunny tempo,
重ねてるのに 愛は解けてゆく
is layered, but love is unraveling.
いつだって worry 心配しちゃってるふり
Always worry, pretending to be worried,
うわついた心まで 正当化しちゃうんだ learn
I even justify my fickle heart, learn.
そもしちゃなかった愛を見つけて
I found a love that wasn't there before,
これが本当の幸せなんだろうなとか思ったり
and I thought, 'This must be true happiness,'
可愛くなるため頑張ったり そのたびフラッシュバックバック浴びて
working hard to be cute, and each time being bathed in flash-back-backs,
常に絶望感に迫られても 守るとか君しか見てないとか言われても
even if I'm constantly pressed by despair, even if I'm told 'I'll protect you' or 'I'm only looking at you,'
真実味ないな
it doesn't sound true.
呼びかけてるのにあの子に夢中で
Even though I'm calling out, you're obsessed with that girl,
絡まってんのに愛がすり抜けいく
it's entangled, but love is slipping away.
チクタクチクタクと流れていく時の針だけが
Tick-tock, tick-tock, only the hands of time flow on,
おいてかないでね おいて
don't leave me behind, leave me.
本当は言いたそう相思相愛 現実的には期待を背負んで
I actually want to say we're mutually in love, but realistically I shoulder expectations,
バッドなエンディング 狂うのもそっちのタイミング
a bad ending, it's also your timing to go crazy.
純愛なんてさ 信じてたのに
Even though I believed in things like pure love,
本命じゃなくて 浮気女は笑
I'm not the one, the cheating woman laughs (lol).
洒落た夜に 溢れたメロディー
In a stylish night, an overflowing melody,
絡まってんのに 愛は解けてゆく
is entangled, but love is unraveling.
シンデレラストーリー 到底違ってるのに
A Cinderella story, though it's completely different,
fake face dance music 嘘まみれに踊ろう
fake face dance music, let's dance covered in lies.
無限ノスタルジー
作詞・作曲：分島花音 / 編曲：千葉"nuts"直樹
Mugen Nostalgia
Lyrics & Composition: Kanon Wakeshima / Arrangement: Naoki "nuts" Chiba
オレンジの太陽 追いかけてきたの
I've been chasing the orange sun.
手の中にあるのは 赤いビー玉
What's in my hand is a red glass marble.
ねぇ あとちょっとだけね それが言いたくて
Hey, just a little bit more, I wanted to say that,
名残サンダル かかと鳴らす
lingering sandals, clicking my heels.
いついつまでも 一人で歩くもん
I'll walk alone forever and ever.
くるくる回って すり抜けいく
Spinning round and round, slipping through.
どこどこまでも 寂しくさせるのよ
It makes me feel lonely no matter where I go.
クスクス笑って 雲の上に居る
Giggling, I'm above the clouds.
君にもう一度 会いたくて
I want to see you once more.
君にもう一度会いたくて
I wanted to see you one more time
帰るには早すぎるでしょ
It's too early to go home, right?
いつも空言で済ました
I always made excuses with empty words
会えるからなんて　不表情に笑わないでね
Saying "we'll see each other." Don't smile without expression.
夕暮れ気圧はプロト
The evening pressure is a prototype
宵の明星を帰り道照らす
The evening star lights up the way home
でもまだ帰れない　だってほら見て
But I can't go home yet. Look,
探し求めたものを追いかけてきたの
I've been chasing what I've been looking for
だから見つけるまで
So until I find it
歩き続けさせて　ねえあとちょっとだけね
Let me keep walking, just a little bit more
それが言いたくて名残サンダル
I wanted to say that in my lingering sandals
忘れて帰るずるっ
I'll forget and go home, slipping away
落ちる夜のパレードに
In the falling night parade
キラキラ光るかけら　そっと浮かべて
Gently floating glittering fragments
落とさないように　ねえ大事にしまってよ
So I don't drop them, please keep them safe
失くさないように
So I don't lose them
左手で握って
Hold them in your left hand
君にもう一度会いたくて
I wanted to see you one more time
行くには早すぎるでしょ
It's too early to go
いつも空言で済ました
I always made excuses with empty words
会えるからなんて　不表情に笑わないでね
Saying "we'll see each other." Don't smile without expression.
夕暮れ気圧はプロト
The evening pressure is a prototype
数えてみたの
I tried counting
空即なんて要らないよ
I don't need things like "emptiness"
迎えに行くから大丈夫
I'll come to get you, so it's okay
コズミックメモリー
Cosmic Memory
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
ということで、ライブももう最後に差し掛かってきました。
And so, the live performance is finally coming to an end.
では皆さん、ラストの告知パートに参りたいと思います！
So everyone, let's move on to the final announcement part!
どんだけ告知あんねんって感じなんですけれども、
You might be thinking, "how many announcements are there?"
あ、その前にちょっとコメント読もうかな。コメント...
Oh, but before that, let me read some comments. Comments...
ちょっと待って、コメント、えーと、あそこに、あそこにあるんだ。
Wait a second, the comments... uh, they're over there. They're over there.
「今来たばっかり！」「もう終わりかー！」嘘でしょ、今来たさん。
“I just got here!” “Is it already over?!” You've got to be kidding me, “Mr. Just Arrived”.
もう44分、はい。
It's already 44 minutes in. Yeah.
「早すぎる！」「まだ来たばっか」「可愛い」あ、ありがとー！
“Too fast!” “Just got here.” “Cute.” Ah, thank you!
ありがとー。コメント。イェーイ。
Thank you. Comments. Yay!
セトリ神すぎ、ありがとうございます。
“The setlist is too divine”, thank you so much.
ということで、告知やっていきたいと思います。
So, let's move on to the announcements.
まずはもう既に出ている情報から参ります。こちら！
First, information that's already out. This!
ZOZOTOWNさんとコラボさせていただくことが発表されております！
It's been announced that we're doing a collaboration with ZOZOTOWN!
3月22日、今日のお昼から受注販売が始まっています。
Pre-order sales started today at noon, March 22nd.
期間は4月12日までですが、受注販売なので
The period is until April 12th, and since it's made-to-order,
急がなくても大丈夫のはず。しかし忘れないようにしてくださいね。
you shouldn't have to rush. But please don't forget, okay?
こちらの商品は、受注販売期間が終わったあと再販する予定がないけど、
There are no plans to resell these items after the pre-order period ends,
可能性はあるとのことです。どうなるか分かりませんがよろしくお願いします。
but there is a possibility. I'm not sure how it'll turn out, but please keep that in mind.
そして、このZOZOTOWNのジャケットを着た星街すいせい等身大フィギュア、皆さんエキスポで見てくださいましたか？こちら！
And, the Hoshimachi Suisei life-sized figure wearing this ZOZOTOWN jacket, did everyone see it at the Expo? This!
こちらの等身大フィギュアが1/7スケールになって発売決定しております！
This life-sized figure has been confirmed for a 1/7 scale release!
こちらのフィギュアは予約期間は5月31日までですので、
The reservation period for this figure is until May 31st, so
えーお財布に余裕がある方は是非ともご購入くださいませ。
for those with some wiggle room in their wallets, please do consider purchasing it.
5月31日までかと思いきや、3月31日までに予約すると、
You might think you have until May 31st, but if you reserve by March 31st,
さいねさん描き下ろしの特製限定ステッカーももらえますので是非チェックしてください。
you'll also get a special limited-edition sticker drawn by Saine-san, so please check it out.
それでは、ZOZOTOWNのアパレルグッズの詳細を見ていきたいと思います。ジャン！
Now, let's take a look at the details of the ZOZOTOWN apparel goods. Ta-da!
まあこんな感じですね。ジャケット、ベレー帽、ベルト、Tシャツ、グッズセット、
Well, it looks like this. A jacket, beret, belt, T-shirt, goods set,
そしてクッションになっております。ぜひ買ってね！
and a cushion. Please buy them!
では、お次。こちら、エキスポで発表ありましたね。すいちゃんとお揃いのなりきりマイクが発売します！
Now, for the next one. This was also announced at the Expo. A “Nariki” (Roleplay) Mic just like Sui-chan's is going on sale!
はい、こちら私が今持っているマイクと全く一緒！めちゃくちゃ似てる。
Yes, this is exactly the same as the microphone I'm holding right now! It looks so much like it.
違う点で言うとすいちゃんのボイスが入ってるっていうところですね。
The difference is that it has Sui-chan's voice in it.
詳細は概要欄にあるバンダイさんのXをチェックしてみて下さい。えーでは皆さん、
Please check Bandai's X linked in the description for details. Well then, everyone,
そこまでは知ってるよと思った皆さん、
For those who thought, "I already know that much,"
ここからは初公開の情報となります！
from here on, the information will be revealed
for the first time!
まずはこちら！
First up is this!
星街すいせい アナログレコード化決定！！
Hoshimachi Suisei Vinyl Record Release Decided!!
この度、これまでリリースしてきました私のアルバムの
My albums that have been released so far
アナログレコード化が決定しました！
are officially getting a vinyl record release!
アナログレコード化って何？と思っている方、
For those wondering, "What's a vinyl record release?"
よく映画とかアニメで出てくるあの古い針を落として、
it's that old thing you often see in movies or anime
where you drop the needle,
ウィーンってクラシックが流れる、あのレコードです。
and that classic sound plays. That's the one.
あのレコードになります！
They're becoming those records!
そしてなんと、第一弾として
And surprisingly, as the first wave,
私のファーストアルバム『Still Still Stellar』のレコードが
the vinyl for my first album, "Still Still Stellar,"
5月22日に発売することになりました！
is set to be released on May 22nd!
この後、21時より各種CDショップにて予約が開始されますので、
Pre-orders will start today at 9 PM
at various CD shops,
概要欄のURLより是非ご確認ください。
so please check the link in the description.
こちらはですね、めちゃくちゃ大きなジャケットになっていて、
These have incredibly large jackets,
超映えるので、レコードがお家にないよって方も
and they look great, so even if you don't have
a record player at home,
是非コレクションとして手に入れていただければと思います。
I hope you'll get one as a collector's item.
レコードはどうやら製造に凄く時間が掛かって、
Apparently, records take a long time to manufacture,
販売数に限りがあるとのことですので、
and there's a limit to how many can be sold,
欲しいなという方はお早めにご予約ください。
so if you want one, please pre-order early.
『Specter』の方に関しても続報をお待ちください。
Please wait for further news regarding "Specter" as well.
そして！めちゃくちゃ嬉しいものがあるんです。見てこれ！
And! There's something I'm incredibly happy about.
Look at this!
カナヘイ×星街すいせいのコラボが決定しましたー！
A collaboration between Kanahei and
Hoshimachi Suisei has been decided!
わー！嬉しい、嬉しい！可愛すぎる！
Wow! I'm so happy! It's too cute!
大好きなカナヘイさんとコラボができるということで、
本当に大人たちありがとうございます。
Being able to collaborate with the Kanahei I love,
thank you so much to all the adults involved.
さらに、このイラストは今回のコラボのために
カナヘイさんに描き下ろしていただきました！
Furthermore, this illustration was drawn specially
by Kanahei for this collaboration!
うわー、カナヘイさん、ありがとう、本当に。
Wow, thank you so much, Kanahei-san.
私がこのカナヘイのうさぎをどれだけ愛しているかというのは、
How much I love Kanahei's Usagi
普段の配信やらX（旧Twitter）やらで分かると思うんですけど、
should be clear from my usual streams and X,
本当に本当に大好きなうさぎちゃんとピスケちゃん、
本当にコラボできて嬉しいです。
so I'm really, really happy to collaborate with
Usagi-chan and Piske-chan, who I love so much.
他にもイラストを描き下ろしてもらっていて、
イラストを使ったグッズ企画も進行中です。
Other illustrations have also been drawn,
and a goods project using them is underway.
詳細は後日改めて告知するので、楽しみに待っていてください。
Details will be announced later,
so please look forward to it.
あー！そして皆さん待ってたよね、
お馴染みの誕生日＆活動6周年記念グッズ。
Ah! And everyone's been waiting for these,
the usual Birthday & 6th Anniversary goods.
はい、バナーです！こちら！今回はこんな感じ。
Here's the banner! This time it's like this.
えっとですね、グッズはちょっと「推し活」っていうものを
テーマに色々作ってみました。
Well, for the goods, I tried making various things
with the theme of "Oshikatsu" (supporting your fave).
まずはフルセットからご紹介。はい、どうぞ。はい。
First, I'll introduce the full set. Here you go.
こんな感じ。フルセットだとこれが全部買えるよ。
Like this. With the full set, you can get all of this.
そしてバラで見ると、はい、B2タペストリー！
And looking at them individually, yes, the B2 Tapestry!
はい、こんな感じ。ちょっとオタ活をしている感じのすいちゃん。
Here it is. Sui-chan looking like she's
doing some "Otakatsu."
ランダムハート型缶バッジ。皆様ランダム本当に申し訳ございません。
Random Heart-shaped Can Badges.
I'm so sorry they're random, everyone.
ランダムで本当に申し訳ございません。ランダムです。ランダムです。
I'm really sorry it's random. It's random.
えっと、今までの周年記念で出したグッズの
Well, they use the key visuals from
キービジュアルをハート型の缶バッジにしました。
past anniversary goods as heart-shaped badges.
めちゃくちゃ可愛いので、ちょっとハートだと痛バ組みにくい
かもしれないけど是非組んでください。
They're super cute, so even if hearts are hard to
fit on an ita-bag, please give it a try.
おでかけすいちゃんのぬいぐるみ。欲しかったよね、これ絶対欲しかったよね。
"Odekake Sui-chan" Plushie. You wanted this,
didn't you? You definitely wanted this.
これは150ミリ、はい、150ミリのすいちゃん。
This is 150mm. Yes, a 150mm Sui-chan.
リハでは「15ミリ」って言っちゃいました。w
I accidentally said "15mm" during rehearsal. lol
150ミリのすいちゃん、お出かけに凄くピッタリ。
是非いろんな所に連れて行ってあげてください。
150mm Sui-chan is perfect for going out.
Please take her to many places with you.
2WAY痛バ For 星詠み。はい、見覚えがあるんじゃないでしょうか。
2WAY Ita-bag for Hoshiyomi. Doesn't it look familiar?
こちら、3月に同じ誕生日のさくらみこさんのほうと
ちょっとお揃な感じ。
This is kind of matching with Sakura Miko-san,
who shares my birthday month in March.
まあ形態だけ、形態だけだよ？
ちょっとお揃な感じにしてみました。
Well, only the style, only the style, okay?
I made it slightly matching.
あの是非こちら使って、痛バ組みやすい感じになってるんで、
Please use this; it's designed to be
easy to assemble an ita-bag.
フロントポケットはクリア素材って書いてあるんで、ここに
缶バッジを連ねていただいて是非お使いください。
The front pocket is made of clear material, so please
line up your badges there and use it.
というものでした。
And that was all of them.
あとはフルセット購入いただいた方には、こちら
箔押し複製サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカードが付いてきます。
Also, for those who purchase the full set,
a foil-stamped signed instax-style card is included.
あ、数量限定ではないです。数量限定ではないので、
Ah, it's not limited in quantity. It's not limited,
こちら買った方全員に、フルセット買った方全員に付いてきます。
是非、是非よろしくお願いいたします。
so everyone who buys the full set will get it.
I hope you'll consider it.
というわけで、立て続けに告知してまいりましたが、
So, I've just given a whole bunch of announcements,
告知物が多すぎて皆ついていけてないとかないよね？
but there were so many that I hope you could
all keep up.
ついていけてるよね？「ビジネスバッグ」ｗ
You're keeping up, right? "Business bag" lol
「ビジテ」も略すなｗ ビジネスてぇてぇを略すなもう。
Don't abbreviate it to "Biz-te" lol
Don't shorten "Business Te-e Te-e."
「戦争回避」ｗ はい、戦争回避です。ｗ
"War avoided" lol Yes, war avoided. lol
というわけで...
Anyway...
次の曲で、
With the next song,
最後になります！
it will be the end!
わぁ、悲しい。もっと聴きたいよ。
Aww, so sad. I want to hear more.
はい。次の曲が実は、
Yes. The next song is actually...
重大告知3つ目なんです！
the third major announcement!
ということは、そう、新曲！
That means, yes, a new song!
新曲を歌う前に、ダンサーさーん！
Before I sing the new song, dancers!
わぁーい！
Yay!
わぁい。この5人で今日の新曲、最後の曲をやりたいと思います。
Yay. The five of us will perform today's new song, the final song.
では、私もちょっと着替えてよろしいですか？
Now, may I go change for a bit?
お着替え参ります。
I'm going to change now.
わぁー！
Whoa!
着替えました。可愛いかな？
I've changed. Do I look cute?
では、このお姿で、みんな行けますか？
Well then, in this outfit, are you all ready?
それでは、聴いてください。
Now then, please listen.
新曲、『ビビデバ』。
New song, 'Bibbidiba'.
つまらないデイズ
Boring days
散々な目
Terrible experiences
奇跡願っているだけの人生
A life just wishing for miracles
WATCH ME DO... 呪術秘中
WATCH ME DO... Secret sorcery
トリック無しのマジック
Magic without any tricks
I WANNA BE FREE だってまだふりだし
I WANNA BE FREE, cause I'm still at the start
(THE PARTY AIN'T STARTED)
HEY タクシー ちょっと宇宙まで
HEY taxi, take me to outer space
秒針は音を立てて
The second hand makes a sound
夜を急かす魔物のよう
Like a monster rushing the night
人生は一瞬にして溶ける魔法
Life is a magic that melts away in an instant
それならば駆け抜けて思い通り！
If so, then run through just as you like!
おしゃまな馬車 飛び乗って
Jump into a stylish carriage
DRIVIN' DRIVIN' DRIVIN'
あたしは大変身メイクアップ！
I'll undergo a huge transformation, make-up!
我儘のまにまに 煌めきに注意
As selfish as I want, watch out for the sparkle
洒落な街で DANCIN' DANCIN' DANCIN'
DANCIN' DANCIN' DANCIN' in the stylish city
左様ならグッバイ劣等感
Well then, goodbye inferiority complex
何時かは喝采クラップオウデエンス
Someday there'll be cheers, clap audience
皆々 ご唱和あれ！
Everyone, sing along with me!
BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOO WA
BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOO WA YEAH
混絡がっても仕様が無いから
Can't be helped if it gets tangled
ガラスシューズで踊る TONIGHT
Dancing in glass shoes TONIGHT
BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOO WA
BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOO WA YEAH
今夜に明日など無い
There's no tomorrow in tonight
ならば自由に踊った者勝ちでしょ
So the one who dances freely wins, right?
DANCE ラリラリホ
DANCE, la-ri-la-ri-ho
どんな問題も解は一つ
Every problem has just one solution
白紙も正解も間違いも
Blank pages, correct answers, and mistakes
愛す本当のあたしの理想
I love them all, my true ideal
何だか世界は限界の気配がして
Somehow the world feels like it's reaching its limit
ただただ安心じゃあ心配
Being just safe makes me worried
じゃあ今すぐ JUMPIN' JUMPIN' OUT
So jump, jump out right now
CHITTY CHITTY BANG BANG CHITTY CHITTY BANG BANG
唯唯若者に危機感抱く日々に
In days of just feeling a sense of crisis as a youth
ぎりぎり爆発気味
On the verge of exploding
たった今発散してしまおうか
Shall I let it all out right now?
まだまだ BIBBIDI 出鱈目に乱射
Still BIBBIDI, firing randomly
一発じゃあ撃ち足りないわ
One shot isn't enough
ついに導き出した君にアンサー
Finally, an answer for you who led the way
灰に成るまで踊って居よう
Let's keep dancing until we turn to ash
BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOO WA
BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOO WA YEAH
おしゃまな馬車 飛び乗って
Jump into a stylish carriage
DRIVIN' DRIVIN' DRIVIN'
あたしは大変身メイクアップ！
I'll undergo a huge transformation, make-up!
我儘のまにまに 煌めきに注意
As selfish as I want, watch out for the sparkle
洒落な街で DANCIN' DANCIN' DANCIN'
DANCIN' DANCIN' DANCIN' in the stylish city
左様ならグッバイ劣等感
Well then, goodbye inferiority complex
何時かは喝采クラップオウデエンス
Someday there'll be cheers, clap audience
皆々 ご唱和あれ！
Everyone, sing along with me!
BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOO WA
BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOO WA YEAH
混絡がっても仕様が無いから
Can't be helped if it gets tangled
ガラスシューズで踊る TONIGHT
Dancing in glass shoes TONIGHT
BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOO WA
BIBBIDI BOBBIDI BOO WA YEAH
今夜に明日など無い
There's no tomorrow in tonight
ならば自由に踊った者勝ちでしょ
So the one who dances freely wins, right?
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you very much!
ビビデバ、この後MV公開！よろしく！
Bibbidiba, the MV will be released right after this! Check it out!
またねー！
See ya!
New single 「ビビデバ」
3/22 24:00 デジタルリリース開始
New single "Bibbidiba"
3/22 24:00 Digital release starts
このあと MV プレミア公開！
MV Premiere coming up next!
重大告知
SheenderellaDay - Hoshimachi Suisei 6th Anniversary -
Major Announcement
start 2024.03.22